wpsnap.com 2016-06-18

# Privacy Policy

Please read the privacy policy below before using this site. Your use of this site indicates your agreement to abide by the terms stated herein. **Content Disclaimer**

All content provided on this site is for informational purposes only.  The Owners of this Site, [WP Snap WordPress Tutorials](https://wpsnap.com/), make no representations as to the accuracy or completeness of any information on this site.   Your use of this site indicates your agreement to not hold The Owners of this Site liable for any incurred losses, injuries, or damages resulting from the use of content contained on this site.

**Information We Collect**

The Owners of this Site own all of the information collected on this site except where explicitly stated.  We collect information when you make information known to us.  This includes when you register for an account, log into an account, post a comment, create a forum post, signup to a mailing list, or interact with us in another form or fashion.  We also collect information via standard web server logging.  This includes information such as your IP address, browser type, date and time of your visits, your internet service provider, etc.  The Owners of this Site reserve the right to reuse,  edit, or delete any content on the site, including user provided content.

**Information Sharing**

We may use information about you to improve our services, but we will not sell or rent your information to third parties.  Your information is only shared with others with your permission, except when required by law.

**E-mail Privacy Policy**

E-mail addresses provided to us will never be rented or sold.  We will only send you relevant content that you opted to receive.  You can register and/or unsubscribe at any time to stop receiving emails from us.

**Legal Disclaimer**

Although we make every effort to protect the privacy of our site visitors, we may have to disclose personal information when required by law.

**Advertisements**

Our privacy policy in regard to displaying Google Ads are as follows:

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on the visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Our site may contain links to affiliate programs, such as Amazon Affiliates.

Our site may also contain paid advertisements from approved vendors.

Please note that The Owners of this Site do not necessarily endorse what is being advertised by other ad serving partners or affiliate program partners.

**Outbound Links**

The Owners of this Site make no representations as to the accuracy or completeness of any information contained on sites we link to.  The Owners of this Site are not responsible privacy practices of sites we link to.  The Owners of this Site are not responsible for any incurred losses, injuries, or damages resulting from the use of web sites we link to.

**Contact Us**

If you have questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.
